{
  "module": {
    "number": 1,
    "name": "chapter1 quiz",
    "questions": 30,
    "revision": "2019-10-13"
  },
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "type": "mc",
      "category": "letter",
      "number": 1,
      "question": "Badchim are the letters in the \n of a block.",
      "answerA": "Bottom",
      "answerB": "Top",
      "answerC": "Right Side",
      "answerD": "Middle",
      "correct_answer": "Bottom?"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "number": 2,
      "question": "The shape of a block of letters in Hangul should be \n.",
      "answerA": "Circular",
      "answerB": "Rectangular",
      "answerC": "Square",
      "answerD": "Triangular",
      "correct_answer": "Square"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "number": 2,
      "question": "Choose the correct t-stop badchim letters.",
      "answerA": "ㄱ, ㄴ, ㅂ, ㅁ, ㅍ",
      "answerB": "ㅋ, ㅌ, ㅊ, ㅍ, ㅎ",
      "answerC": "ㅎ, ㄹ, ㅇ, ㄴ, ㅁ",
      "answerD": "ㄷ, ㅅ, ㅈ, ㅊ, ㅌ",
      "correct_answer": "ㄷ, ㅅ, ㅈ, ㅊ, ㅌ"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "number": 2,
      "question": "ㅎ is most similar to the English '\n' sound.",
      "answerA": "H",
      "answerB": "N",
      "answerC": "Ng",
      "answerD": "J",
      "correct_answer": "H"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "number": 2,
      "question": "ㅍ is most similar to the English '\n' sound.",
      "answerA": "J",
      "answerB": "N",
      "answerC": "K",
      "answerD": "P",
      "correct_answer": "P"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "number": 2,
      "question": "ㅁ is most similar to the English '\n' sound.",
      "answerA": "P",
      "answerB": "M",
      "answerC": "N",
      "answerD": "D",
      "correct_answer": "M"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "number": 2,
      "question": "ㅅ is most similar to the English '\n' sound.",
      "answerA": "K",
      "answerB": "J",
      "answerC": "S",
      "answerD": "T",
      "correct_answer": "S"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "number": 2,
      "question": "ㅊ is most similar to the English '\n' sound.",
      "answerA": "T",
      "answerB": "Ch",
      "answerC": "J",
      "answerD": "B",
      "correct_answer": "Ch"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "number": 2,
      "question": "ㅌ is most similar to the English '\n' sound.",
      "answerA": "K",
      "answerB": "D",
      "answerC": "T",
      "answerD": "Ch",
      "correct_answer": "T"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "number": 2,
      "question": "ㅋ is most similar to the English '\n' sound.",
      "answerA": "G",
      "answerB": "K",
      "answerC": "M",
      "answerD": "N",
      "correct_answer": "K"
    }
  ]
}